So, um, coming back to the account that
created the pull request or if you were
working by yourself, this will be just
your same normal account. You can see
here on the top bar, it says that our
pull request was merged. We can even
open up the commit details. Um, and we
can see that our multiplier.js is now on
the main branch. What that means is the
main copy of code has all of our changes
and we don't need our branch anymore.
So, um, come over here to GitHub desktop
and we can click fetch origin.
And that um syncs our version of code
with the code in GitHub. But we don't
need our branch anymore. So what we're
going to do is we're going to right
click on it. We're going to open up our
dropown. We're going to right click on
our branch and we're going to click
delete. Now it's going to say it can't
be undone. And do you want to delete it
in GitHub as well? Well, it says this
branch also exists on the remote. The
remote means somewhere out on the
internet, wherever our code is being
stored, this branch also exists there
because we published it in a prior
video. So, what we're going to do is
yes, we do want to delete it there as
well. We're going to click this checkbox
and we're going to click delete.
Now, our function is gone. I mean,
sorry, now our branch is gone. And we'll
click fetch origin. What fetch origin
does is it compares our code with the
code out on GitHub. Now we can click
open in Visual Studio Code and we can
see that multiply.js is on our computer.
If we come over here, we can see we are
on the main branch. Originally
multiply.js was not on the main branch,
but now it is on the main branch. So the
main version of our code has all of the
changes from our previous branch.
Now um you never ever ever want to
develop on main. So, you're going to
keep following this pattern where you um
create a new branch
and then
you open it in Visual Studio Code.
You make changes.
You save those changes.
You come over to GitHub.
desktop. You write a message about what
you did.
You publish your branch.
You create a pull request.
Here you create your pull request. You
say what you did. You create your pull
request. And then someone can come on,
look at what's happening, and then merge
the pull request.
And once that's done, um, you're back to
deleting your branch again. And as long
as you keep following this process where
you make a branch, you make your
changes, and you merge it back, um,
using a pull request, you'll be
following what's called the GitHub flow.
Hope that was helpful. Thanks for
watching.